wpromote.com 2019-12-07

# Wpromote's Privacy Policy | Wpromote

WPROMOTE, LLC ("WPROMOTE" or "www.wpromote.com" or "we" or "us") has created this privacy policy (this "Privacy Policy") in order to demonstrate its commitment to user, visitor and customer privacy with regard to the WPROMOTE web site at www.wpromote.com (the "Website"). Privacy on the Website is of great importance to us. Because we gather important information from our users, visitors and customers (collectively "Customers" or "you" or "your"), we have established this Privacy Policy as a means to communicate our information gathering and dissemination practices. By accessing this Website, you acknowledge and agree to this Privacy Policy and also agree to the Terms of Use of the Website. 

## Information We Collect And How We Make Use Of It

We require Customers who register to use the services offered on our Website (collectively, the "Service") to give us personally identifiable information, which may include but is not limited to the Customer’s first and last name, company name, address, phone number, email address, credit card number, cookies, IP logs, and other information (collectively "Personal Information"). Besides the Personal Information, we may also collect other information regarding your use of the Website, including general statistical or aggregate information, which may be collected whether or not you register for the Services offered on our Website. From time to time, we may also collect or ask for additional Personal Information, which will also be expressly included herein as Personal Information. You can opt out of providing this additional information by not entering it when asked or not using the Website, although not providing it may hinder your ability to use the Website. 

We use the Personal Information and the information that we collect to provide and maintain the Website as we deem appropriate in our sole discretion. We may also use the information to contact you to further discuss interest in our company, the services that we provide, and to send information regarding our company or partners, such as promotions and events. You may be invited to receive an email newsletter or other correspondence by providing an email address. We may also email (or send via other methods) information regarding updates to the Website or WPROMOTE, and may send a customer newsletter, or other correspondence. You will have an opportunity to unsubscribe to any emails or mailings by clicking on an "unsubscribe" hyperlink contained in promotional emails we send you, or by e-mailing us at our Customer Service Department. Any opt-out by you is not deemed valid until processed by WPROMOTE. It is your obligation to verify that you have been opted-out. WPROMOTE shall not be liable for problems with the opt-out procedures. 

Except as we explicitly state at the time we request information, or as provided for herein or in the WPROMOTE Terms of Use Agreement, we do not disclose to third parties the information provided. All financial and billing information that we collect through the Website is used solely to check the qualifications of prospective customers and to bill for the Service. This billing information is not used by WPROMOTE for marketing or promotional purposes, except as provided for herein. We may use a third-party intermediary to manage the credit card processing and we may share any appropriate information with them. 

In addition, we may share or disclose your information, including Personal Information, in the following situations: 

  * We reserve the right to disclose any Personal Information or other information if required to do so by law, including compliance with legal process served on WPROMOTE, or if we believe that such action is necessary in order to (a) protect or defend the legal rights or property of WPROMOTE, the Website or its Customers, or (b) in an emergency to protect the health and safety of the Website’s users or the general public.
  * Personal Information you submit, and other information we collect, may be shared with our parent, subsidiaries, affiliates, licensors, licensees, joint venturers, partners, sponsors and/or vendors (collectively, “Affiliated Third Parties”) to perform customer service, carry out your requests, respond to inquiries, and to notify you regarding any promotions, purchases or account information. 
  * Personal Information you submit, and other information we collect, will be disclosed as part of any merger or acquisition, creation of a separate business to provide the Website or fulfill our services, sale or pledge of company assets as well as in the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership in which Customer information would be transferred as one of the business assets of the company.
  * Personal Information you submit, and other information we collect, may be distributed or shared in order to conduct any business as we, in our sole subjective discretion, deem reasonable.

We do not respond to browser do-not-track signals or mechanisms.

You may be using the Website to host data (including but not limited to pictures, email correspondence with other users and other content) and information ("Data"). We will not review, share, distribute, print, or reference any such Data except as provided herein and in the WPROMOTE Terms of Use, as may be required by law, or in order to conduct any business that we, in our sole subjective discretion, deem reasonable. Individual records may at times be viewed or accessed for the purpose of resolving a problem, support issue, suspected violation of any of the terms of this Website, as may be required by law, or as deemed necessary by WPROMOTE. Of course, you are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality and security of your user registration and password. 

WPROMOTE may also collect certain information from visitors to, and users of, the Website, such as Internet addresses. This information is logged to help diagnose technical problems, and to administer our Website in order to constantly improve the quality of the Service. We may also track and analyze non-identifying and aggregate usage and volume statistical information from you and provide such information to third parties. 

WPROMOTE does not wish to collect any Personal Information (or any information at all) from any persons under 14 years old. If you are under 14 years old, you may not use the Website. 

## Anti-Spam Policy

Wpromote.com subscribes to an Anti-Spam policy for all its communication protocols. This means that we do not condone unsolicited email messages, notifications, alerts or any message that you may receive from someone who should not have your email address. 

If you have received an unsolicited email message, which you would like to report to Wpromote please inform us via email at: [emailviolation@wpromote.com](mailto:emailviolation@wpromote.com). 

The following two options are available:

  * Inform Wpromote of the incident, but keep your email unblocked, or
  * Inform Wpromote of the incident and have your email blocked so as to not be able to receive any messages sent via Wpromote.

Please include your email address, the date and time you received it and the contents of the message (if possible) when completing the email. 

## Personally Identifiable Information

**Personally Identifiable information (PII) Defined:** Any information or combination of information that identifies, links, or is unique to a person. PII can be broken into two different categories: sensitive and non-sensitive. PII is defined as sensitive when, if lost or compromised, it could potentially result in harm or identity theft. Non-sensitive PII is defined as publicly available information. This pertains to both client and client’s customer data.

Examples of PII (Not all inclusive) : 

Sensitive | SSN, Driver’s License, Birth Date, Birthplace, Cell phone, Personal email or mailing address, Employment information  
---|---  
Non-sensitive | Office location, Business phone number, Business email address  

**Sensitive PII Handling:**

  * Sensitive PII will not be transmitted through attachments within email or other communication tools that are not encrypted. 
  * All sensitive PII data is to be stored and shared directly through specific cloud tools to ensure encryption while not in use - Google Drive, Box, Dropbox. 
  * Permission to data will only be shared with those that have been agreed to be working on the specified tasks. 
  * No personal accounts will have access to sensitive PII data.
  * No personal laptops or devices will be used to access sensitive PII data.
  * When sensitive PII data is provided through insecure means, data is to be moved to one of the specified cloud tools and any local files that may have been stored is to be deleted. 
  * Once sensitive PII data isn’t needed anymore, delete all data previously stored.
  * If it’s required to store sensitive PII on a local storage device, the hard drive must be encrypted. 

## Third Party Websites

The Website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these other websites. You will need to check the policy statement of these others websites to understand their policies. When you access a linked site you may be disclosing private information. It is your responsibility to keep such information private and confidential. 

## Cookies

When you view our Websites, we may store some information on your computer's hard drive. This information will be in the form of a "Cookie." Cookies enable us to establish the shopping cart session and allow you to purchase products on-line at our site. Most web browsers automatically accept Cookies, but you can change your browser to prevent that. Without accepting a Cookie, you can browse through our site, but you will be unable to establish a shopping cart session and make a purchase on-line. 

## Security

The Website makes a reasonable effort to protect your information by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology. SSL encrypts your information to ensure it remains private and secure. WE DO NOT REPRESENT, WARRANT AND/OR GUARANTEE THAT PERSONAL INFORMATION WILL REMAIN SECURE. To check the security of your connection, look at the bottom of your browser window after accessing the server. If you see an unbroken key or a closed lock (depending on your browser), then SSL is active. You can also check by looking at the URL line of your browser. When accessing a secure server, the first characters of the site will change from "http" to "https". 

## Additional Information

This Policy is part of the Terms of Use of the Website and any use of the Website is governed by those Terms of Use. Questions regarding this Policy or the practices of the Website should be directed to WPROMOTE’s Administrator by emailing such questions to contact@wpromote.com or by certified mail addressed to WPROMOTE, LLC, 2100 E. Grand Ave. First Floor El Segundo, CA 90245, Attn: Privacy Policy Administrator. 

## Updates To Our Policy

If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will post a notice on this Website notifying users of the changes. In some cases, we also may send an email notifying users of the changes. You should check this Website periodically to see if any recent changes to this Privacy Policy have occurred. If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, you should contact our Customer Service Department. 

## How To Contact Us

If you have any questions regarding the Wpromote privacy policy or information that you have submitted to us, please feel free to contact us at: 

  * Email: [contact@wpromote.com](mailto:contact@wpromote.com)
  * Mailing Address: Wpromote LLC 2100 E. Grand Ave. First Floor El Segundo, CA 90245
